[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
We've built a model.
我们已经建立了一个模型
We understood it's accuracy about 0.911%.
我们知道了它的准确率是91.1%
Let's go and actually use this model for something, something actually quite cool.
让我们来使用这个模型去做一些酷酷的事情
So what I'm gonna do is Apply the model.
也就是我要做的 应用模型
Learned model to understand sentiment for
通过训练的模型来分析我们的朋友
our friend, the Giraffe.
Giraffe 的情感状况
So, here we go.
那么我们开始吧
Let's understand it a little bit.
一步一步来
So here's what I'm gonna do.
这是我接下来要做的
I'm going to take those giraffe_reviews that I built a little bit earlier.
我要在我之前建立的giraffe_reviews里面
And, I'm gonna create a new column to this
然后我准备添加新的一列
giraffe_reviews called my predicted_sentiment.
叫做predicted_sentiment(预测情感)
And this predicted_sentiment is gonna come from
这个predicted_sentiment
taking the sentiment model that we build.
会是我们建立的情感分析模型中所得到的预测
The sentiment model, and oops,
sentiment model 额糟了
this auto-complete was a little slow, sorry about that.
自动填充功能有一点点慢 很抱歉
Oh man, we have a little glitch there.
抱歉 出了一点小状况
So Okay, we'll take the sentiment model and
恩 我要用这个sentiment_model
we're going to call this function predict on it.
在后面输入.predict来预测
And we'll try to predict how does it feel about the giraffe_reviews.
这就是我们如何让模型来预测giraffe_reviews（我们朋友giraffe的点评）
So how do you feel about my friend: the giraffe_reviews.
也就是你对我们的朋友giraffe是什么样的情感
And the output, and this is a key thing,
结果 是最重要的东西
we're not just gonna output the zero-one,
我们 不会让结果变成简单的0或者1
where they predict the sentiment to be zero or one.
通常模型的结果会是0或者1
I'm gonna say output probability And if you remember,
我想让结果是概率 如果你还记得的话
we just talked about this in the module, that by outputting probability,
我们之前说过 通过输出概率结果
you can get a more fine grain estimate what the prediction looks like.
我们可以得到一个更加精确的预测结果
So, we just run it and
我们先运行一下程序
just let's take a quick look at what this new giraffe_reviews look like.
然后快速的看一些结果怎样
So let's look at the head of this table, and you'll see that now we have
看一下表格的抬头 你会看到
the name of the product, the review, the rating, the word count.
我们有产品的名字 点评 评分 文字计数
And I added another column called the predicted sentiment.
然后我添加了新的一列 叫做预测情感
And for some reviews it's really high 0.999, 0.99,
有些点评可以高达0.999 0.99
and here's a review that's pretty low sentiment.
这是一个典型的情感评分比较低的点评
There should really be a large warning on the,
也就是说有很多不好的点评在里面
they don't like it for some reason, now let's try to understand.
他们可能某种原因不是很喜欢 让我们试着理解一下
Let's look at the reviews and see what reviews are positive or
让我们看一下点评 并且了解 哪些点评是正面的
negative and see what the people are saying about the product.
哪些是负面的 和人们怎么说这些产品
So here's what I'm gonna do.
这是我接下来要做的
We're gonna sort
我要排序
the reviews based on the predicted
排序那些基于预测情感的点评
sentiment and explore.
并且深入研究
And the cool thing here is the predicted sentiment is a much more fine grain
很酷的是 这里预测的情感是比普通的方法更为精致的描述
description of whether we've used positive or negative.
比之于只用是否是正面还是负面
The stars are really skewed, five stars, four stars, three stars, one star, and
评星系统有些偏态分布了 五星 四星 三星 一星
this will tell you how far along the spectrum you are.
评星系统会告诉你 你大概在哪个部分（几颗星）
But now that we have this numbers, this extra column, we can do a lot more.
但是这个额外的一列 有着确切的数字 我们就可以研究更多了
So I'm gonna take this giraffe data, and I'm going to sort it.
所以我要把Giraffe的数据 排序
So all I have to do is take it, take the same value, and I'm gonna call
我要做的就是取一些值 然后用sort 这个函数
the function sort on it.
进行排序
And you have to see, what column you're sorting based on.
你可以看到你在排序哪一列
So we're gonna sort based on this new column
我们将会基于新的一列进行排序
that we call predicted_sentiment.
叫做predicted_sentiment
And one little trick here, we're gonna say ascending is equal to false.
小技巧 我们用的使ascending（升序） 等于False（否）
So we're still sorting that ascending order is gonna start in descending order.
也就是说我们要降序排序
Starting from the most positive reviews down to the most negatives.
从最正面的评价排序到最负面的评价
Now that we've sorted it we're gonna just show the first few lines of the table.
我们已经排序完了 我们准备显示这个表格的前几行
And what you should see is that the reviews are now sorted
你会看到这个表格会基于
based on that sentiment.
情感预测而排序
So the very top here, we have the most positive one has predicted
所以说在最顶上 我们有着最正面的评价
sentiment of 1.9999 and they all sorted.
他们预测了是0.999 然后依次排序
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community